# **AUSTIN FISK**

Http://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~fisk/ | 608-393-5902 | fiskaustin.af@gmail.com

# **Education and Training**

University of Wisconsin - Madison — Madison, WI, USA Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Graduated: May 2018

### Overview

Proven Embedded Software Engineer with 4+ years of experience. I excel in bringing up hardware from Rev 1 to Release. My expertise is in Embedded C with branches out into many other areas of engineering such as PCB Design, 3D Design, and Automobile Data. My personal projects display a wide array of my engineering experience. These projects are available for viewing at <a href="https://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~fisk/">https://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~fisk/</a>. The 433Mhz Remote and Pool Monitoring Machine display the largest array of skills such as Embedded Firmware, Web Server, Circuit/PCB Design, and 3D Design.

# Experience

#### **Embedded Software Engineer**

**HP Tuners** — Buffalo Grove, IL

Embedded C

Hardware bring up

12C, SPI, and CAN

TX/RX for 315/433MHz as well as 125KHz signals

Bootloader an App with OTA updates

Persisting variables through low power states

PIC Flash Programming

PCB Design

#### **Embedded Software Engineer**

Jan 2021 to Aug 2022

Aug 2022 to Current

Reconyx — Verona, WI

Developed embedded C code for the system UI, built upon the iCatch V37 Image processor Persisting and loading user configuration settings

I2C communications between the House Keeper and the Image Processor chip as well as various other devices

## **Test Automation Developer**

Jan 2019 to Current

**MCANTA** — Madison, WI

Working with customers and fellow employees to assist in their robotic process automation development. Copado and Eggplant platforms.

#### Skills

- Programming Languages: C, Python, Java, Visual Basic, Assembly, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, SenseTalk, PaceWords
- Optimization/Speed: Multi Thread on Embedded Systems, Bus Traffic Configuration, Power Saving, Interrupts, Measuring Speed with Ossilloscope
- Failure Evaluation: Photo Metadata, Firebase Queries

- User Interface Design: UI Mock Up, UI Design, Persisting Options
- Hardware Skills: Simple PCB Design, Oscilloscope, Logic Analyzer, Soldering
- Additional Trainings: Automotive Electrical 1, 2, & 3. Chip Whisperer. C++ Design Patterns. C++ advanced class. PCB Full Spectrum (Altium). Embedded System Security for C/C++ Developers.